MAITRAY SUTHAR

+918866194206

maitraysuthar@gmail.com

 $-\Box$

 $-\Box$

maitraysuthar.github.io/portfolio/

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & SOFTWARE SOLUTION PROVIDER

PROFILE

More than 4.5 years of experience of software engineering, implementing leading, and launching software products. Skilled in agile processes, backend, frontend, and web development, object-oriented and functional programming. Well suited for the industry and bringing ideas to life.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (PHP)

FEB 2018 - Present

Cygnet Infotech. Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN Roles and Responsibilities:

- Web Development with PHP and React.
- API Development with PHP Laravel, Nodejs.
- Project deploy (Amazon EC2, cPanel). Worked with Docker.
- Teamwork with QA and BA. Small team management.
- Test-driven development.
- Project & Client Handling. Successfully deployed several projects.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (PHP)

JUN 2016 - FEB 2018

Estatic Infotech. Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN

Roles and Responsibilities:

- Web Development with PHP and Angular 2+.
- API Development with PHP Laravel.
- Teamwork with QA and BA. Test-driven development.
- Project & Client Handling.
- Successfully deployed several projects.
- Project deployment (Amazon EC2 Instance, C Panel)

PHP DEVELOPER

JUN 2013 - OCT 2014

Steamlite Pvt Ltd. Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN

Roles and Responsibilities:

Web Development with PHP and JQuery.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth: 28-05-1993.

Marital Status: Single.

Languages: English (Proficient), Hindi (Fluent) Gujarati (Native).

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING 2013 - 2016
INFORMATION & TECHNOLOGY

Gujarat Technological University

DIPLOMA OF ENGINEERING 2010 - 2013

INFORMATION & TECHNOLOGY

Gujarat Technological University

SKILLS

MySQL

JavaScript

HTML / CSS

Python

MongoDB

PERSONAL SKILLS

Problem Solving

Adaptability

Team Leading

TECH SKILLS

Proficient: React JS, Laravel, Angular, Node JS, Express JS, Codeigniter, REST API. Payment Gateways, Chat, Socket.

Basic: Django, Yii2, Web design, React

Native